Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Subject Files
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 9)
  - Montana. Labor Dept., 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 10)
  - Montana. Lands and Investments Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 11-12)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 13)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 14)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 15)
  - Montana. Motor Vehicles, Registry of, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 16)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 17)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 18)
  - Montana. Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 19)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 20)
  - Montana. Personnel Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 21)
  - Montana. Prison, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 22)
  - Montana. Public Employees Retirement System, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 23)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 24)
  - Montana. Public Service Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 25)
  - Montana. Public Welfare Dept., 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 26)
  - Montana. Railroad Commissioners, Board of, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 27)
  - Montana. School for Deaf and Blind, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 28)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 29)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 30)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 31)
  - Montana. State Hospital (Warm Springs), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 32)
  - Montana. State Industrial School for Boys, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 33)
  - Montana. State Training School (Boulder), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 34)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 35)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 36)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 37)
  - Montana. Trade Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 38)
  - Montana. Treasurer, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 39)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 40)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls (Mountain View), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 41)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 42)
  - Montana. Western Montana College of Education, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 43)
  - Mortgages, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 44)
  - Nepotism, 1954 (Box-folder 47 / 45)
  - Nurses, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 46)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 47)
  - Paroles and pardons, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 48)
  - Pension, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 49)
  - Photography, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 50)
  - Pinball machines, 1954 (Box-folder 47 / 51)
  - Press releases, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 1)
  - Printing, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 2)
  - Prisoners, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 3)
  - Proposed legislation (includes county sheriffs and attorneys), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 4-5)
  - Requests for information, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 6-11)
  - Requests for opinion, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 12)
  - Resolutions, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 13)
  - Roads, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 14)
  - Salaries, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 15)
  - School transportation, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 16)
  - Schools, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 17)
  - Soil conservation, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 18)
  - Taxation, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 19)
  - Unions and labor, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 20)
  - Vacation leave, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 21)
  - Veterans, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 22)
  - Veterans Bonus, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 23)
  - Water and water courses, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 48 / 24)
  - Admission to the Bar, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 25)
  - Adoption, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 26)
  - Appointments, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 27)
  - Architecture, 1955 (Box-folder 48 / 28)
  - Attorneys General, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 29-32)
  - Automobiles, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 33)
  - Banks, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 34)
  - Bonds, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 35)
  - Carey Land Act, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48 / 36)
  - Cedar Creek gas and oil hearings, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 49 / 1-3)
  - Children, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 4)
  - Chiropractors, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 5)
  - Claims, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 6)
  - Complaints, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 7-11)
  - Contests, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 12)
  - Contracts, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 13)
  - Copies of laws, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 14)
  - Corporations, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 15)
  - Council of State Governments, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 16)
  - County Assessors, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 17)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead-Custer, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 49 / 18-21)
  - County Attorneys: Daniels-Yellowstone, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 1-13)
  - County Auditors, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 14)
  - County Clerks, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 15)
  - County Commissioners, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 16)
  - County Sheriffs, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 17)
  - County Superintendents of Schools, 1955 (Box-folder 50 / 18)
  - County Surveyors, 1956 (Box-folder 50 / 19)
  - County Treasurers, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 20)
  - Criminal cases, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 21)
  - Criminal identification, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 22)
  - Disbarment, 1955 (Box-folder 50 / 23)
  - Doctors and hospitals, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 50 / 24-27)
  - Elections, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 1)
  - Employment, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 2)
  - Estates: General, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 3)
  - Estates: Escheated, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 4)
  - Experiment station, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 5)
  - Extradition, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 6-7)
  - Fences, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 8)
  - Fire arms, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 9)
  - Fire departments, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 10)
  - Forestry, 1956 (Box-folder 51 / 11)
  - Future Farmers of America (FFA), 1955 (Box-folder 51 / 12)
  - Gambling: General, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 13-14)
  - Gambling: Beaverhead-Yellowstone counties, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 15-27)
  - Grass conservation, 1955 (Box-folder 51 / 28)
  - Indians, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 29)
  - Insurance, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 30-32)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 51 / 33)
  - Investigations, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 1)
  - Irrigation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 2)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 3)
  - Lands, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 4)
  - Law enforcement, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 5)
  - Law Enforcement Conference, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 6-7)
  - Laws, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 8-9)
  - Leases, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 10)
  - Licenses, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 11)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 12)
  - Military service, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 13)
  - Mines and mining, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 15)
  - Montana Citizens Freight Rate Association, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 16)
  - Montana. Adjutant General, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 17)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 18)
  - Montana. Athletic Commission, 1955 (Box-folder 52 / 19)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 20)
  - Montana. Bank Examiner, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 21)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber Boards, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 22)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 23)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 24-27)
  - Montana. Engineer, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 28)
  - Montana. Equalization Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 52 / 29-30)
  - Montana. Examiners, Board of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 1)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 2-4)
  - Montana. Governor, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 5)
  - Montana. Hail Insurance Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 6)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 7)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 8-10)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 11)
  - Montana. Historical Society, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 12)
  - Montana. Hospital (Warm Springs), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 13)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 14-15)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 16)
  - Montana. Institutions (miscellaneous), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 53 / 17)
  - Montana. labor Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 1)
  - Montana. Laboratories Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 2)
  - Montana. Lands and Investments, Dept. of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 3-5)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 6-7)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 8)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 9)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 10)
  - Montana. Motor Vehicles, Registrar of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 11)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 12)
  - Montana. Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 13)
  - Montana. Old Age Home (Lewistown), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 14)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 15)
  - Montana. Personnel Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 16)
  - Montana. Planning Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 17)
  - Montana. Prison (includes Floxley and Company), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 18-19)
  - Montana. Public Employees Retirement System, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 20-22)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 23)
  - Montana. Purchasing Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 24)
  - Montana. Railroad and Public Service Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 25)
  - Montana. School for Deaf and Blind, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 54 / 26)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 1)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 2)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 3)
  - Montana. State Controller, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 4)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 5)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 6)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 7)
  - Montana. Trade Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 8)
  - Montana. Training School (Boulder), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 9)
  - Montana. Treasurer, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 10)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Sanitarium (Galen), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 11)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 12)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls (Mountain View), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 13)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 14)
  - Montana. Welfare Dept., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 15-17)
  - Montana. Western Montana College, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 18)
  - Mortgages, 1955 (Box-folder 55 / 19)
  - Narcotics, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 20)
  - Naturalization, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 21)
  - Nepotism, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 22)
  - Nurses, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 23)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 24)
  - Oil lease law, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 25-28)
  - Osteopathy, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 29)
  - Pardon and parole, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 30-31)
  - Pension, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 32)
  - Pharmacy, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 33)
  - Photography, 1955 (Box-folder 55 / 34)
  - Plumbing Examiners, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 35)
  - Press releases, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 36)
  - Printing, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 37)
  - Prisoners, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 38)
  - Proposed legislation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 55 / 39)
  - Proposed legislation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 1)
  - Public utilities, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 2)
  - Recommendations, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 3)
  - Reports of Attorney General, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 4)
  - Request copy of opinion, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 5)
  - Requests for information: A-Z, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 6-16)
  - Roads, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 17-18)
  - Salaries, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 19)
  - School transportation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 20)
  - Schools, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 21-22)
  - Soil conservation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 23-24)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 25)
  - Taxation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 56 / 26-27)
  - Unions, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 1)
  - Vacation leave, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 2)
  - Veterans, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 3)
  - Veterans' bonus, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 4)
  - Vocational rehabilitation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 5)
  - Water and water courses, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 57 / 6)
  - Adoption, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 7)
  - Architecture, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 8)
  - Attorneys General, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 9-10)
  - Automobiles, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 11)
  - Banks, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 12)
  - Bonds, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 13)
  - Capital land grant, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 14)
  - Carey Land Act, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 15)
  - Children, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 16)
  - City-County planning boards, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 17)
  - Claims, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 18)
  - Complaints, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 19-21)
  - Contests, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 22)
  - Contracts, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 23)
  - Copy of law, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 24)
  - Corporations, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 25)
  - Council of State Governments, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 26-27)
  - County Assessors, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 28)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead - Musselshell, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 57 / 29-37)
  - County Attorneys: Park-Yellowstone, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 1-4)
  - County Auditors, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 5)
  - County Clerks, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 6)
  - County Commissioners, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 7)
  - County Sheriffs, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 8)
  - County Superintendent of Schools, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 9)
  - County Treasurers, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 10)
  - Criminal cases, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 11)
  - Criminal identifications, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 12)
  - Doctors and hospitals, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 13)
  - Elections, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 14)
  - Employment, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 15)
  - Estates, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 16)
  - Estates: escheated, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 17)
  - Extradition, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 18)
  - Fences, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 19)
  - Firearms (re guns), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 20)
  - Fire Depts., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 21)
  - Forestry, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 22)
  - "Free Zoo" (confidence game), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 23-24)
  - Gambling (includes reports of D.A. Batchoff), 1957-1962 (Box-folder 58 / 25-26)
  - Gambling: Beaverhead-Yellowstone counties, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 58 / 27-32)
  - Gambling investigation: Highwood, 1957 (Box-folder 58 / 33)
  - Grass conservation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 34)
  - Indians, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 35)
  - Insurance, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 58 / 36-37)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 1-2)
  - Investigations, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 3)
  - Irrigation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 4)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 5)
  - Lands, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 6-7)
  - Law enforcement, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 8)
  - Law Enforcement Conference, 1958 (Box-folder 59 / 9)
  - Laws, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 10-11)
  - Leases, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 12)
  - Libraries, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 13)
  - Licences, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 14-15)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 16)
  - Medical Examiners, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 17)
  - Mines and mining, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 18)
  - Montana. Adjusted Compensation Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 19)
  - Montana. Adjutant General, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 20-21)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 22)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 23)
  - Montana. Bank Examiner, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 24)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber Boards, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 25)
  - Montana. Controller, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 26)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 27)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59 / 28-31)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 1-3)
  - Montana. Equalization, Board of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 4)
  - Montana. Examiners, Board of (includes minutes), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 5-6)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 7)
  - Montana. Governor, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 8)
  - Montana. Hail Insurance Board, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 9)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 10)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 11)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 12)
  - Montana. Historical Society, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 13)
  - Montana. Hospital (Warm Springs), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 14)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 15)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 16)
  - Montana. Labor Dept., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 17)
  - Montana. Laboratory Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 18)
  - Montana. Lands and Investments, Dept. of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 19)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 20)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 21)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 22)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 23)
  - Montana. Old Age Home (Lewistown), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 24)
  - Montana. Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 25)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60 / 26)
  - Montana. Prison, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 1)
  - Montana. Prison: architect's drawings, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 2)
  - Montana. Prison: Council on Corrections, 1957 (Box-folder 61 / 3)
  - Montana. Prison: report on conditions, 1957 (Box-folder 61 / 4)
  - Montana. Prison: riot (includes transcript of hearings), 1957-1959 (Box-folder 61 / 5-9)
  - Montana. Public Employees Retirement System, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 10-11)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 12)
  - Montana. Purchasing Dept., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 13)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 14)
  - Montana. Registrar of Motor Vehicles, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 15)
  - Montana. School for Deaf and Blind, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 16)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 61 / 17)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 1)
  - Montana. Soldiers' Home, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 2)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 3)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 4-5)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 6)
  - Montana. Taxation Education Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 7)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 8)
  - Montana. Training School (Boulder), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 9)
  - Montana. Treasurer, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 10)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Sanitarium (Galen), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 11)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 12)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls (Mountain View), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 13)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 14)
  - Montana. Welfare Dept., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 15-16)
  - Montana. Western Montana College, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 17)
  - Montana Stockgrowers Association, 1957 (Box-folder 62 / 17a)
  - Nepotism, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 18)
  - Nurses, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 19)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 20)
  - Oil lease law, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 21)
  - Open Montana Committee, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 22)
  - Pardon and parole, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 23)
  - Pension, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 24)
  - Printing, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 25)
  - Prisoners, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 26-27)
  - Proposed legislation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 28)
  - Prostitution, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 29)
  - Public utilities, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 30)
  - Requests for copy of opinions, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 31)
  - Requests for information: A-Z, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 32-38)
  - Resolutions, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 39)
  - Roads, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 40)
  - Salaries, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 41)
  - Salk vaccine (re polio), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 42)
  - School transportation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 43)
  - Soil conservation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 44)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 62 / 45)
  - Taxation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 1-2)
  - Unions (labor), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 3)
  - Vacation leave, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 4)
  - Veterans, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 5)
  - Veterans' bonus, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 6)
  - Vocational rehabilitation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 7)
  - Water and water courses, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 63 / 8)
  - Adoption, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 9)
  - Advance fees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 10)
  - Appropriations (should be in box 48), 1955-1957 (Box-folder 63 / 11)
  - Attorneys General, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 12)
  - Banks, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 13)
  - Bonds, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 14)
  - Capital Land Grant, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 15)
  - Children, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 16)
  - Chiropractors, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 17)
  - Complaints, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 18)
  - Contracts, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 19)
  - Council of State Governments, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 20)
  - Counties: Beaverhead-Yellowstone, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 21-27)
  - County Assessors, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 28)
  - County Auditors, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 29)
  - County Clerks, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 30)
  - County Commissioners, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 31)
  - County Sheriffs, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 32)
  - County Surveyors, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 33)
  - County Treasurers, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 34)
  - Criminal cases, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 35)
  - Criminal identification, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63 / 36)
  - Elections, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 1)
  - Escheated estates, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 2)
  - Estates, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 3)
  - Extradition, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 4)
  - Fire departments, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 5)
  - Indians, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 6)
  - Insurance, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 7)
  - Investigations, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 8)
  - Irrigation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 9)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 10)
  - Land, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 11)
  - Law enforcement, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 12)
  - Law Enforcement Academy, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 13-18)
  - Law Enforcement Conference, 1959 (Box-folder 64 / 19)
  - Laws, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 20)
  - Leases, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 21)
  - Libraries, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 22)
  - Licenses, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 23)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 24)
  - Mines and mining, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 26)
  - Montana. Adjusted Compensation Division (re Korean War Bonus), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 27)